Pierre Hilliard

Warehouse worker and forklift driver.

Chicago, IL pierrehilliard28@yahoo.com 2175166597

Several years in the warehouse industry also customer service looking utilize my skills. I have experience driving forklift, warehouse associate, and customer service. Eager to work in a call center or warehouse environment.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Sitdown forklift

Central Transport - Hillside, IL February 2016 to October 2018

Driving forklift and loading freight and unloading.

Sales Associate/ forklift

Sams club - Northlake, IL June 2015 to December 2017

Team lead ,stocker, fork lift driver, unloading trucks, customer service, interact with customer on a daily basis answering questions about products. Also recommend to try different items that may assist the products that they actually inquired.

Receiving Associate , customer service, cash register

Walmart - Northlake, IL November 2014 to April 2015

Load unload trucks, help customers, and use the cash register.

Casual Mail Handler (Seasonal)

United States Postal Service - Forest Park, IL August 2012 to June 2013

Load and unload trucks. Sort mail and scan mail bags before loading the bins.

Casual Mail Sorter

United States Postal Service - Elk Grove Village, IL March 2011 to May 2012

Casual Unloading trucks sorting mail 03/2011 to 05/2012

Education

High school Diploma in Manufacturing

chicago job corp - Chicago, IL

Associate in Criminal justice administration

Triton College - Melrose Park, IL 2016

Skills

forklift, welding, warehouse worker, customer service,

Certifications/Licenses

Forklift Certified

November 2009 to Present

I've received my forklift certification through Chicago job corp. stand up, sit down, and cherry picker Im most experienced in.

Additional Information

Looking for growth and advancement in my job search to endure and utilize all my skills to be an asset to a company for growth.